[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120319pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 45, "question": "Mrs. Santorum, how are you?", "question_tokens": ["Mrs.", "Santorum", ",", "how", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 46, "answer": "Hi, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Hi", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mrs. Santorum"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120319pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 61, "question": "But the fact that they all prayed for you, did you feel now you've been strengthened by the power of prayer from that audience before you confront me?", "question_tokens": ["But", "the", "fact", "that", "they", "all", "prayed", "for", "you", ",", "did", "you", "feel", "now", "you", "'ve", "been", "strengthened", "by", "the", "power", "of", "prayer", "from", "that", "audience", "before", "you", "confront", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 62, "answer": "That's good.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rick"]}, "docId": "120319pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 68, "question": "How do you think he's fairing?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "think", "he", "'s", "fairing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 69, "answer": "Piers, Rick is amazing.", "answer_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "Rick", "is", "amazing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120319pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 98, "question": "You know, there's a bit of work to be done here, isn't there, Karen?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "there", "'s", "a", "bit", "of", "work", "to", "be", "done", "here", ",", "is", "n't", "there", ",", "Karen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 99, "answer": "I'm working on it, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "working", "on", "it", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Karen"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120319pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 109, "question": "What did you think of that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "think", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 110, "answer": "Exactly.", "answer_tokens": ["Exactly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120319pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 138, "question": "Is he anti-us having contraception?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "anti-us", "having", "contraception", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 139, "answer": "Not at all.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120319pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 140, "question": "Well, what is his view?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "what", "is", "his", "view", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 141, "answer": "Not at all.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120319pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 155, "question": "When you say he'll do nothing on the contraception issue, do you mean that if he was to become president that he would basically respect a woman's right to have contraception if that's what she chose to do?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "say", "he", "'ll", "do", "nothing", "on", "the", "contraception", "issue", ",", "do", "you", "mean", "that", "if", "he", "was", "to", "become", "president", "that", "he", "would", "basically", "respect", "a", "woman", "'s", "right", "to", "have", "contraception", "if", "that", "'s", "what", "she", "chose", "to", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 156, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120319pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 176, "question": "How often do you pick that phone up and say, Rick, you shouldn't have said that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "often", "do", "you", "pick", "that", "phone", "up", "and", "say", ",", "Rick", ",", "you", "should", "n't", "have", "said", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RP", "CC", "VB", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 177, "answer": "Well, we talk a lot throughout the day, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "talk", "a", "lot", "throughout", "the", "day", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rick"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "120319pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WP", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 224, "question": "If he does, why should American women also love your husband?", "question_tokens": ["If", "he", "does", ",", "why", "should", "American", "women", "also", "love", "your", "husband", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "WRB", "MD", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 225, "answer": "Well, because he's a man who cares deeply about the heart and soul of America.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "because", "he", "'s", "a", "man", "who", "cares", "deeply", "about", "the", "heart", "and", "soul", "of", "America", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120319pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 323, "question": "What the hell that does that mean?", "question_tokens": ["What", "the", "hell", "that", "does", "that", "mean", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 324, "answer": "I'm going to have to ask her.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "going", "to", "have", "to", "ask", "her", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120319pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", ":", "WP", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 328, "question": "What do you think -- what do you think she meant?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "--", "what", "do", "you", "think", "she", "meant", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 329, "answer": "Well, I think when you're dealing in snippets with little sound bites you really don't get the full picture of -- who somebody is.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "when", "you", "'re", "dealing", "in", "snippets", "with", "little", "sound", "bites", "you", "really", "do", "n't", "get", "the", "full", "picture", "of", "--", "who", "somebody", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120319pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 348, "question": "When she was on bended knee proposing, what were you thinking?", "question_tokens": ["When", "she", "was", "on", "bended", "knee", "proposing", ",", "what", "were", "you", "thinking", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "VBN", "NN", "VBG", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 349, "answer": "I said, oh, my gosh.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "said", ",", "oh", ",", "my", "gosh", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120319pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 396, "question": "It's getting completely out of hand and actually becoming destructive to the party?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "getting", "completely", "out", "of", "hand", "and", "actually", "becoming", "destructive", "to", "the", "party", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VBG", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 397, "answer": "Well, first of all, I believe there are good people on both sides of almost every issue in that regard.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "I", "believe", "there", "are", "good", "people", "on", "both", "sides", "of", "almost", "every", "issue", "in", "that", "regard", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120319pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "RB", "VB", "TO", "NNP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 444, "question": "What's the problem?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "problem", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 445, "answer": "ROWN: Well, you'd have to certainly speak to Mitt and his team.", "answer_tokens": ["ROWN", ":", "Well", ",", "you", "'d", "have", "to", "certainly", "speak", "to", "Mitt", "and", "his", "team", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120319pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RBR", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 457, "question": "Is it an issue, do you think, his friends slightly -- it frustrates you that he can't get that side over?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "an", "issue", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "his", "friends", "slightly", "--", "it", "frustrates", "you", "that", "he", "ca", "n't", "get", "that", "side", "over", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "PRP$", "NNS", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 458, "answer": "Well, I know that when it comes to dealing with the economic issues, there's no one I would trust more than Governor Romney.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "know", "that", "when", "it", "comes", "to", "dealing", "with", "the", "economic", "issues", ",", "there", "'s", "no", "one", "I", "would", "trust", "more", "than", "Governor", "Romney", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120319pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 498, "question": "What it Gene Simmons singing through the screen?", "question_tokens": ["What", "it", "Gene", "Simmons", "singing", "through", "the", "screen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 499, "answer": "No phones, no iPad.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "phones", ",", "no", "iPad", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Simmons"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120319pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 501, "question": "What is it with you and Gene Simmons?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "it", "with", "you", "and", "Gene", "Simmons", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 502, "answer": "Actually, I went to a Kiss concert.", "answer_tokens": ["Actually", ",", "I", "went", "to", "a", "Kiss", "concert", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gene Simmons"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120319pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 601, "question": "You actually want me to comment on that?", "question_tokens": ["You", "actually", "want", "me", "to", "comment", "on", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 602, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Massachusetts"]}, "docId": "120319pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 623, "question": "How do you personally feel about that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "personally", "feel", "about", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 624, "answer": "Well, it's settled law in Massachusetts.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "settled", "law", "in", "Massachusetts", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120319pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 663, "question": "How do you keep America great?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "keep", "America", "great", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 664, "answer": "You need to -- we need your debt and deficit under control.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "need", "to", "--", "we", "need", "your", "debt", "and", "deficit", "under", "control", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120319pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 665, "question": "Other than that?", "question_tokens": ["Other", "than", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 666, "answer": "No, that's the key.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "that", "'s", "the", "key", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120319pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 667, "question": "Assuming you do that, what else do you do to -- to maintain America's greatness in the world?", "question_tokens": ["Assuming", "you", "do", "that", ",", "what", "else", "do", "you", "do", "to", "--", "to", "maintain", "America", "'s", "greatness", "in", "the", "world", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", ",", "WP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", ":", "IN", "NN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 668, "answer": "You need to create jobs.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "need", "to", "create", "jobs", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Apple"]}, "docId": "120319pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 679, "question": "What is wrong with that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "wrong", "with", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 680, "answer": "Have the president from Apple on.", "answer_tokens": ["Have", "the", "president", "from", "Apple", "on", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "120319pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 681, "question": "What do you think of that argument?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "that", "argument", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 682, "answer": "I think that you need to make America competitive again.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "you", "need", "to", "make", "America", "competitive", "again", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120319pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 711, "question": "That's it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 712, "answer": "That's it.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120319pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 715, "question": "You have so much more to say, right?", "question_tokens": ["You", "have", "so", "much", "more", "to", "say", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "RBR", "TO", "VB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 716, "answer": "I do.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120319pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 728, "question": "Frank, how are you?", "question_tokens": ["Frank", ",", "how", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 729, "answer": "I'm good.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Green Room"], "PERSON": ["Karen Santorum", "Scott Brown"]}, "docId": "120319pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "TO", "DT", "DT", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 730, "question": "How are you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 731, "answer": "You've been out there in the Green Room listening to all this, Karen Santorum and then Scott Brown.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "'ve", "been", "out", "there", "in", "the", "Green", "Room", "listening", "to", "all", "this", ",", "Karen", "Santorum", "and", "then", "Scott", "Brown", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120319pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 735, "question": "Is it their fault that we've been debating little else but abortion and contraception and other social issues like that?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "their", "fault", "that", "we", "'ve", "been", "debating", "little", "else", "but", "abortion", "and", "contraception", "and", "other", "social", "issues", "like", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "CC", "NN", "CC", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 736, "answer": "To a large extent, yes, it's been embedded in the dynamics of the Republican primary.", "answer_tokens": ["To", "a", "large", "extent", ",", "yes", ",", "it", "'s", "been", "embedded", "in", "the", "dynamics", "of", "the", "Republican", "primary", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120319pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 751, "question": "Were you surprised to hear her say that?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "surprised", "to", "hear", "her", "say", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 752, "answer": "It was interesting the way she said it.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "interesting", "the", "way", "she", "said", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120319pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ":"], "qSentId": 781, "question": "Who would have a better chance of beating Barack Obama, very quickly?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "would", "have", "a", "better", "chance", "of", "beating", "Barack", "Obama", ",", "very", "quickly", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 782, "answer": "Not --", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Romney"]}, "docId": "120319pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 783, "question": "Santorum or Romney, we'll offer two?", "question_tokens": ["Santorum", "or", "Romney", ",", "we", "'ll", "offer", "two", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "CC", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 784, "answer": "Romney, Romney.", "answer_tokens": ["Romney", ",", "Romney", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120319pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "WP", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "CC", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 788, "question": "-- who's president?", "question_tokens": ["--", "who", "'s", "president", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "WP", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 789, "answer": "It depends on what happens between now and then.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "depends", "on", "what", "happens", "between", "now", "and", "then", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120319pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 790, "question": "Once answer?", "question_tokens": ["Once", "answer", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 791, "answer": "Not doing that.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "doing", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]